now we've enjoyed in developing this
technology in a way as a retrofit energy
system in other words what good is it to
put it in the home heating you have no
fuel source to be able to run the trucks
and operate the automobiles what good is
that if you don't have an energy source
that you cannot put in the industry and
maintain the industrial base what good
is it for example if you cannot be able
to maintain aviation you know during the
Arab embargo we also is confronted with
another problem
the problem being is that at that
particular time the United States
government had only two and a half days
of aviation fuel for global context the
day it's down to the day of the quarter
when it reaches a day supply joins Jesus
stack will have to make the decision no
more global defence it is you ever hear
anything about the war burgers if you
want to study about history of world war
one world war two will start to realize
there were men specially trained and
women trained in order to bring
countries in the war to break their
economic back to take over the control
of their countries you ever hear of the
council Foreign Relations the Trilateral
Commission you ever hear about the
council the hoods of 300 you hear about
the internationalist that are
controlling to bring in a one-world
government now we're heading for one
world government but unfortunately if
the one world government is headed under
a control is controlled by Mussolini and
Mussolini or Hitler or person filled
with demonic spirit we're in one head
for power is that Democratic Society of
the world government would be more
representative each country of the world
then in fact we could be able to
stabilize as people upon the earth the
attitude that the multi dimensions is to
come up with zero growth in deficit
growth zero population growth when I was
making a presentation and UNITA 2:52
represenation z-- there I was blocked in
presenting the
ecology not because the viability of the
technology because the international
attitude is they do not want industrial
growth to be maintained there is a move
to try to force the countries to accept
that they would sign over the natural
resource rights if you signed over your
natural resource rights you have taken
over the countries without even firing a
shot this is the help bring in the
one-world government
the number one thing that will defuse
the entire episode to be able to
maintain us is to bring an alternate
energy source in that we competed with
sustain and maintain not only an
industrial base of this country further
the world and therefore I will share
this information with you and once I
share it with you you have a
responsibility
I'm sharing a responsibility to you so
great now the power structures to be we
all hear about the guys invented the
carburetors that go 200 miles per hour
and go heavy and they never get out of
the market area we talked about high
energy systems a development of high
technology and they never seem to get
out in the marketplace why is that you
know in a rockefeller Rockefeller was a
very smart man to get our economies to
operate on fossil fuel you got a hold of
a think tank and anything take he says I
want you to come up with motivating
thoughts that would deem ultimately
motivate the people in order to bring us
up on the fossil fuels you see at that
time we're talking about high energy
research and development or we're not in
the end Rockefeller wanted to convince
the population world that we need fossil
fuels to maintain the economy and
therefore suppress and prevent altered
energy sources to come forward and so in
this think tank he came up with such
trivialities or you can always lead a
horse to water but you can't get in the
drink any of you've ever said that you
know if you say that out of your mouth
you know that you believe it it's your
greatest lie on the world if you lead a
horse to water he doesn't want to drink
I will show you if you're staking about
four feet away from the water two and
two days flat you'll try to break the
rope if you want if you want to speed up
your process feeds insult and
another gate Modi voted 85 but you can't
city hall how about another than
with the motivating is I two things you
never discusses politics and religion do
you know why in the news media's that
you are bombarded with tremendous
negative because they had found out the
physical psychological makeup of an
individual is such that if you receive
so much negative you turn it off
do you know the defy our forefathers and
our grandfathers were there waking out
of their graves and see what's taking
place in our country today do you know
what happen David van der arm you go to
Washington DC and clean out our
government absolutely the negatives and
is presenting to you is the process of
desensitizing you to allow such
atrocities to take over and if you don't
think that there are people in the world
that do not want America at the stand
you know why because a constitution in
the United States the Bill of Rights
says as free people we have ability to
enjoy certain enable rights that was
given to us by God and unfortunately
there are some people who does not want
us to continue to enjoy their freedom
that our forefathers fought and when I
turned and said I will do this Lord it
had to be by faith because I was given a
great gift that death was to be raised
under fear
now let's see how it gives water is fuel
because the greatest thing that all
political leaders fear that you and I
would come together and one Accord that
if you and I would come together in one
Accord no political system in the world
no multi the nationalist group could
defeat you but what happened to Russia
after seventy years they said so we no
longer one communism we're tired of the
KGB killing our people who tortured our
people and said enough is enough
and that's why you receive the negative
that's why a nice
conferences that they will try to
promote and try to tell you that you
have not the power of say-so are in our
government and I want to tell you that
under the Constitution in the United
States readeth or it gives us the
ultimate power to be able to determine
the destiny and the strength of our
country and how I bring in this
technology in it can't come through the
multi international structures if I
would sign over this technology the gel
electrical Westinghouse then we'd be
taken over within 24 hours if you think
you've got political pressures in the
United States government trying to
negotiate with the military for their
political pressures are straight and
they cry out and you know when the herbs
came to me and offered me a billion
dollars cold cash simply to stop on the
technology and when I said no I will not
do this and he said you will be stopped
and I said why is that
he said because the apathy of the
American people is such that they will
not come behind me and for a long time
that statement stood out but I will
assure you today not only in the United
States but in the world that they're
coming together in one Accord and say
it's enough because if we do not pre
versus however recently come back from
Sweden they're tired force are dying
why because the pollutants the polluting
glutens that it's one in the air
covalently linking up with the
ionosphere is decreasing the light
intensity coming into this atmosphere
and as a result of this decrease in
light intensity bacteria is now allowed
to grow which is now causing blight this
is now starting to kill our trees
forward and look in the black forest
that even the trees and the roots are
dying we are on a planet which is our
Bishop and if we do not reverse if we do
not come together in one Accord then I
would say doing that we will not survive
now when we show this technology
you must now make the decision whether
or not you come together in one Accord
and try and we can do it to come
together keep this winter storm as well
as to protect it and when President
Reagan was devised this technology he
turned against the multinationals and
said do not fly or do not allow this
technology to go forward and he wrote
the executive action to ensure that this
technology will not only be protected
for the United States but also to be
protected for the world and is amazing
to me that we have the abilities that we
could proceed on doing the first thing
and always being the first objective and
always will be the first objective
developing the technology you must
legalize it first and then bring it in
many inventors blow their ego they get
to their Achilles heel to try to obtain
the information not for the benefit of
Umi but the benefit of control or
manipulation or suppression of that
technology so when you develop your high
technology you do everything possible
the prime objective is a legalized
technology when you receive that gold
seal and that little red ribbon it says
that you have complied for the laws when
is the not so it's not what Stan Meyer
says it's what is now been legalized and
if there's any question of operability
of the technology under the wall whether
they have before you under u.s. code 35
years code one-on-one and show
operability and when we showed
operability of this technology
then it became a great concern meant to
protect this technology for all the
countries as well as the United States
so as I move there are many people who
have seek to try to cost me to stumble
and try to seek to suppress me is trying
to seek in many ways but the Lord has
always allowed that we can proceed on
with the technology as we're legalizing
the technology I'm subject to the
national security laws of this country
I'm also subject to the national
security laws of other countries of the
ect Treaty Act other countries who now
are informed that this type of
technology is requesting that this
technology will also be protected for
their countries for you see if this Tec
type of technology is restricted from
those other countries then their entire
economic base could collapse you know if
you can use water as a fuel source to
maintain in the salvation of one country
but it is locked in another you can drop
the prices or new puts in commodities
and therefore the other country cannot
be able to sustain itself unfortunately
there are those who seek power
controlled by greed
right and seems to have the desire to
control man under v it's a form of this
sickness and unfortunately in my many
battles we've had to overcome this type
in order to bring this technology out so
you'll have to forgive me for those who
feel that I have should have brought the
technology up further I had to be in
compliance the both of us and an exit
security laws in the PCT treaty act in
order to get around the loopholes that
are set they're not for you and I what's
up there to control and manipulate the
high technology and so if you never
violate that blind directive you can
bring it in good water is fuel you know
coming in here today have driven a car
here and have you driven cars at all
you realize that when you're driving on
gasoline you know that you're running on
a hydrogen you know that if you look at
the if you look at the chemical equation
of gasoline you will find out the
hydrogen atom is attached the carbon
atom is not so and basically in the
highest octane of gasoline you have
roughly about a half a pound of hydrogen
- now water on the other hand is two to
one 201 oxygen is not so how many pounds
of hydrogen do we have in water you find
out by the atomic weight is around 1.7
pounds of hydrogen in water I had the
most scientific population study on
hydrogen that's ever come out as a
scientific world from NASA we not propel
the Columbus bishop by hydrogen and
oxygen and in that report it clearly
stipulated the hydrogen was the most
ideal fuel of the future it can be
utilized anywhere salt even the
environmental pollution problem but they
did not have an answer in three areas
one to produce the hydrogen gas or
release it economically from water
control the rate of production be able
to adjust the burn rate of hydrogen gas
to equal the fossil fuels and at the
port one be able to transport it without
spark ignition with all that noise both
national and international this type of
technology to be able to use water as a
fuel source